<?xml version="1.0"?>
<evemon xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <newest>
    <date>10 July 2011</date>
    <version>1.4.1.2798</version>
    <url>http://forum.battleclinic.com/index.php/topic,147155.0.html</url>
    <autopatchurl>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/installers/EVEMon-install-1.4.1.2798.exe</autopatchurl>
    <autopatchargs>/S /AUTORUN /SKIPDOTNET</autopatchargs>
    <additionalargs>/D=%EVEMON_EXECUTABLE_PATH%</additionalargs>
    <message><![CDATA[== Breaking Changes ==

* Due to merging of the BattleClininc API settings files, user will have to re-enter BattleClinic API credentials and setting for this feature.

== Contributors for this version ==

* Jimi
* evilek

== Bug Fixes ==

* Fixed a visual bug in Industry monitor where scroll bar position isn't persistent.
* Fixed an issue where the whole skill queue remaining time is shown in G15 (third line) instead of the skill's.
* Fixed an issue when clicking the Cancel button of Blank Character Creator window, it doesn't close the window.
* EVEMon will now handle better similar opened window, remembering the position of the last closed one.
* EVEMon will again display all market orders.
* Fixed a visual bug where a long Bio info gets wrapped to a second line.
* Fixed an issue where an order gets not removed from the list (if it's the only one) due to change made by CCP to the Market Orders API call.
* Fixed an issue in Skill Explorer where the prerequisites of a blueprint wasn't corresponding to its activity.
* Fixed a crash bug in Skill Browser when skill tree is reset and user right clicks on a blank spot.

== Enhancements ==

* In case only one skill level is in training and info cycling is enabled, G15 LCD will display the skill in training instead of the queue finish time.
* Blank Character Creator window will now have the same behavior as other EVEMon windows.
* An opened plan will now notify if it contains obsolete entries upon entries completing training.

== Misc ==

* Renamed "Add" button to "Import" in Blank Character Creator.
* Feature info in Feature window have been updated.
* Switched OrderID to 64bit (see related devblog -  http://www.eveonline.com/devblog.asp?a=blog&bid=924).
* EVEMon will temporarily display again market orders notifications in a not so accurate way, till CCP fixes the Market Orders API.
* Some menu items in main EVEMon window have been re-arranged in alphabetical order.]]></message>
  </newest>
  <datafiles>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-blueprints-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>28 July 2011</date>
      <md5>37994de8daa4b4faf03c9f6a112c3e42</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incarna/273475b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.0.1 (273475b) blueprints data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-certificates-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 July 2011</date>
      <md5>f995acff5a87c9bb7cdf2376938469cc</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incarna/273475b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.0.1 (273475b) certificates data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-geography-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>28 July 2011</date>
      <md5>2a043ccbbcc91c9b8257399070a3504c</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incarna/273475b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.0.1 (273475b) geography data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-items-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>28 July 2011</date>
      <md5>a7c1126184d23aed1d17647debefaf8e</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incarna/273475b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.0.1 (273475b) items data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-properties-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>28 July 2011</date>
      <md5>ca754909732f33dcf811e50da0c0f87d</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incarna/273475b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.0.1 (273475b) properties data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-reprocessing-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 July 2011</date>
      <md5>322a64607ae565e7d0af03ea9bfc9783</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incarna/273475b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.0.1 (273475b) reprocessing data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-skills-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 July 2011</date>
      <md5>73ecf3d1f20e9acfe5cfeae221f89fd0</md5>
      <url>http://evemon.static.battleclinic.com/builds/updates/Incarna/273475b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.0.1 (273475b) skills data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
  </datafiles>
</evemon>