<?xml version="1.0"?>
<evemon xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <newest>
    <date>20 November 2011</date>
    <version>1.5.2.3179</version>
    <md5>b657ad66a3d9fcb5ab8072f3b44ce790</md5>
    <url>http://forum.battleclinic.com/index.php/topic,154855.0.html</url>
    <autopatchurl>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/downloads/EVEMon-install-1.5.2.3179.exe</autopatchurl>
    <autopatchargs>/S /AUTORUN /SKIPDOTNET</autopatchargs>
    <additionalargs>/D=%EVEMON_EXECUTABLE_PATH%</additionalargs>
    <message><![CDATA[== Contributors for this version ==

* Jimi
* Kelos Pelmand
* lerthe61

== Bug Fixes ==

* Fixed a bug where sender id of an EVE notification wasn't parsed correctly.
* Fixed a visual bug in character monitor when active ship name exceeds panel width.
* Fixed issues with HTML special characters in EVE mail titles.
* Fixed a visual bug in cache timer error page of the API Key Importation window.
* Fixed an issue where character list in API key management window is not updated when updating API key after an error.
* Fixed a crash bug in Certificate browser.
* Fixed a visual bug in Overview when skill training is completed and there is no skill in queue.
* Fixed a visual bug of the monitor timer upon first selection of a character tab.
* Fixed potential crash bug in ship loadouts feature.
* Fixed a visual bug (completion date) in footer info when printing a plan.
* Fixed a bug where skill level entries where removed after canceling in 'Remove entries from plan' window.
* Last State Change info will now be shown correctly in Market orders monitor.
* Last State Change info will now be shown correctly in Industry jobs monitor.
* Fixed a visual bug in Industry jobs monitor where job state does not get updated when job is ready.
* Fixed an bug where prerequisite skill for a blueprint was presented multiple times in tooltip, in the Skill Explorer.
* Fixed a bug where clicking the 'copy details' in the exception handler window causes the operation to fail.
* Fixed a visual bug in SkillExplorerWindow when using larger fonts settings.

== Enhancements ==

* Added support for Corporation type API keys. Corp Market orders and Industry jobs issued by a character are again available.
* Improved the way EVEMon is handling notifications about EVE database inaccessibility and expands the range of notifications about database related errors.
* Added support for unicode characters in EVE mail bodies and EVE notification texts.
* Enhanced the way the columns are sized in each monitor.
* Improved the way ignored characters and characters with more than one associated API key are displayed in API key deletion window.
* Assigned buttons for 'Enter' or 'Esc' key pressing in API keys Importation window. Resolved issue with 'Import', 'Update' button not having focus when on last page.
* Negative balance will be now shown in red.
* MD5Sum check will now prevent from installing a corrupt EVEMon installer via the auto-updater.
* Added auto-size ability via preferences menu item selection in each monitor with columns.
* Enhanced the way column sizes in skill planner.
* Upon a new release auto-update, the data files will get deleted, assuring that the next time EVEMon starts it loads the newest data files.
* Changed the notification behavior on EVEMon startup.
* Added a button in settings that opens the EVEMon's data directory.
* Enhanced the visual feedback in ship loadout window.
* Each ship loadout window now describes the plan it's bound to. Each Plan window can now open its own ship loadout window.
* EveIDtoName file is now saved upon collecting the data and not when EVEMon closes.
* An informative tooltip is now shown when hovering over an Industry job.
* Skill selection updates through out the entire Skill Planner. Noticable effect when toggling the 'Owns book' in skill browser and 'Mark as owned/unowned' in plan queue.

== Misc ==

* Updated format of EFT exporting for CAK.
* Removed the link in 'Help' to 'EVE Online Q&A' as the project is deleted.
* Several improvements have been done to the base code to make EVEMon a better application.]]></message>
  </newest>
  <datafiles>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-blueprints-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>24 November 2011</date>
      <md5>115c91c2a4a21fc1e4d9054f07bb1c02</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Incarna/306979b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.1 (306979b) blueprints data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-certificates-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>24 November 2011</date>
      <md5>9fa59cae413770fa90c547bd46edab57</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Incarna/306979b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.1 (306979b) certificates data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-geography-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>24 November 2011</date>
      <md5>77d0209251919ddc8d8e07046d2195c7</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Incarna/306979b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.1 (306979b) geography data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-items-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>24 November 2011</date>
      <md5>a21161b81908dd75fa2755e58a89cfe2</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Incarna/306979b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.1 (306979b) items data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-properties-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>24 November 2011</date>
      <md5>6de9e0c12cc805aaa31bf934023a9384</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Incarna/306979b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.1 (306979b) properties data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-reprocessing-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>24 November 2011</date>
      <md5>75f2c25c7277b26d8501364189c7e765</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Incarna/306979b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.1 (306979b) reprocessing data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-skills-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>24 November 2011</date>
      <md5>217beb6e168f15bdd4105605ecb0d203</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Incarna/306979b</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Incarna 1.1 (306979b) skills data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
  </datafiles>
</evemon>