<?xml version="1.0"?>
<evemon xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <newest>
    <date>06 April 2012</date>
    <version>1.6.1.3611</version>
    <md5>fcdd61fd97ec0bf22236dbcc54399e16</md5>
    <url>http://forum.battleclinic.com/index.php/topic,162875.0.html</url>
    <autopatchurl>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/downloads/EVEMon-install-1.6.1.3611.exe</autopatchurl>
    <autopatchargs>/S /AUTORUN /SKIPDOTNET</autopatchargs>
    <additionalargs>/D=%EVEMON_EXECUTABLE_PATH%</additionalargs>
    <message><![CDATA[== Contributors for this version ==

* Jimi
* Jazzy_Josh

== Bug Fixes ==

* Fixed a bug in EVE Notifications Monitor where every sender was shown as a corporation.
* Fixed various issues when choosing Outlook as external calendar.
* Fixed some minor visual bugs when displaying courier contracts details.
* Fixed a visual bug where corporation name in Employment History monitor wasn't updating correctly.
* Fixed a bug where Overview was not placed in the correct position when restoring settings.
* Fixed a visual bug where when restoring settings the tip window visibility wasn't following settings.
* Fixed a bug where EVEMon was notifying when an update was initiated and the character was removed since.
* Fixed a bug where the character list in API Tester was not updated when collection of characters changes.
* Fixed a bug where the character list in Characters Comparison was not updated when collection of characters or monitored characters changes.
* Fixed a bug where any open windows were not closed when reseting or restoring settings or hide or deleting characters.
* Fixed a bug where tray icon was visible after restoring main window while settings for 'Show System Tray Icon' is set to 'When Minimized'.
* Fixed a crash bug when an Implant set gets deleted while is selected in Plan Editor.
* Fixed several memory leaks when restoring or resetting settings.
* Fixed a bug in Contracts where the names of assignee and acceptor where not updated.
* Fixed the link to EVE-Dev site.
* Fixed a bug where controls that accept vCode was restrained to fewer digits than allowed.
* Fixed several issues that can lead to crash when machine is missing fonts.

== Enhancements ==

* Blueprint browser filter now takes into consideration the activity when showing the 'blueprints I cannot use'.
* Added ability to load settings directly from the storage server on EVEMon startup.
* Added the remaining API calls to API Tester feature.

== Misc ==

* Several improvements have been done to the base code to make EVEMon a better, faster and more stable application.]]></message>
  </newest>
  <datafiles>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-blueprints-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>29 March 2012</date>
      <md5>b2438ac642ce716f2bc8d99cd09eeb4c</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Crucible/355549</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Crucible 1.6 (355549) blueprints data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-certificates-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>29 March 2012</date>
      <md5>a47cc5f2a8d8687b4ef17cb310474c44</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Crucible/355549</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Crucible 1.6 (355549) certificates data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-geography-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>29 March 2012</date>
      <md5>58c7c7f018af4e560d437f70383680d9</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Crucible/355549</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Crucible 1.6 (355549) geography data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-items-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>29 March 2012</date>
      <md5>d0385d9fde85fbd0e7d0c65c3069a173</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Crucible/355549</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Crucible 1.6 (355549) items data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-properties-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>29 March 2012</date>
      <md5>0ca8efc6b98414dd8a40f70c3ce626a6</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Crucible/355549</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Crucible 1.6 (355549) properties data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-reprocessing-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>29 March 2012</date>
      <md5>0d97c378866cce63766ada1df69f815b</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Crucible/355549</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Crucible 1.6 (355549) reprocessing data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-skills-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>29 March 2012</date>
      <md5>aa74354942dfad9527ca1da564b525ce</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Crucible/355549</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Crucible 1.6 (355549) skills data file by the EVEMon Development Team]]></message>
    </datafile>
  </datafiles>
</evemon>