<?xml version="1.0"?>
<evemon xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <newest>
    <date>10 June 2012</date>
    <version>1.7.0.3809</version>
    <md5>dc5390d1836dd63b7237479b5a62a263</md5>
    <url>http://forum.battleclinic.com/index.php/topic,166187.0.html</url>
    <autopatchurl>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/downloads/EVEMon-install-1.7.0.3809.exe</autopatchurl>
    <autopatchargs>/S /AUTORUN /SKIPDOTNET</autopatchargs>
    <additionalargs>/D=%EVEMON_EXECUTABLE_PATH%</additionalargs>
    <message><![CDATA[== Contributors for this version ==

* Jimi

== New Features ==

* EVEMon now has a character Asset monitor.
* EVEMon now has a character Wallet Journal monitor.
* EVEMon now has a character Wallet Transactions monitor.
* EVEMon now has a Market Unified Uploader.
* EVEMon now has a character Factional Warfare monitor.

== Bug Fixes ==

* Fixed a crash bug when Overview tab is the last in Tab collection.
* Fixed a bug where the installation for an industry job is wrongly assigned.
* Fixed a bug where plan entries where not getting correctly removed internally upon restoring a plan.
* Fixed a visual bug with search text not reseting upon changing monitor.
* Fixed a visual bug when ampersand is used in user entered text in Character Info.
* Fixed a bug when sorting by 'Quantity' in Market orders monitor.
* Fixed a bug where google calendar wasn't updating the correct event.
* Fixed a visual bug in API keys management window when using large fonts.
* Fixed a bug in Skill browser where selecting an owned skill had unwanted behavior.
* Fixed an bug where a character is added in monitoring collection after it has been deleted.
* Fixed a visual bug where the notification about insufficient balance was not updated when character balance was updated.
* Fixed a bug where contact notifications type where not shown correctly.
* Fixed a bug where blueprint selector was losing focus when using search list.

== Enhancements ==

* Industry jobs that have been completed but not delivered, even passed the max period EVEMon tracks them, will now be shown.
* Tooltip in any monitor has infinite display time and is displayed hovering over at any position.
* Tooltip in Plan Queue has infinite display time and is displayed hovering over at any position.
* An informative tooltip is shown when similar items are selected in Asset monitor.
* Added selections to enable or disable all in features menu.
* Added an informative text when no character is monitored and overview tab is disabled.
* Adding ability to export to csv, monitored info (where it makes sense).
* Solar systems and locations are now colored according to their security level.
* EVEMon will now notify only for unread EVE notifications.

== Misc ==

* Several improvements have been done to the base code to make EVEMon a better, faster and more stable application.]]></message>
  </newest>
  <datafiles>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-blueprints-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 June 2012</date>
      <md5>567c52efe3a3b8762b70934a383b69f9</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Inferno/376700</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Inferno 1.0 (376700) blueprints data file by the EVEMon Development Team
NOT COMPATIBLE with EVEMon prior to version 1.7.0]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-certificates-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 June 2012</date>
      <md5>c9eaa52747814eb186432d1a1fbe2de0</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Inferno/376700</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Inferno 1.0 (376700) certificates data file by the EVEMon Development Team
NOT COMPATIBLE with EVEMon prior to version 1.7.0]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-geography-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 June 2012</date>
      <md5>3b130c6507b33c9a9cf165e9a77c6ced</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Inferno/376700</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Inferno 1.0 (376700) geography data file by the EVEMon Development Team
NOT COMPATIBLE with EVEMon prior to version 1.7.0]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-items-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 June 2012</date>
      <md5>5b060cc87bc890593d8553a35631f4a0</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Inferno/376700</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Inferno 1.0 (376700) items data file by the EVEMon Development Team
NOT COMPATIBLE with EVEMon prior to version 1.7.0]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-properties-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 June 2012</date>
      <md5>b510b9759fb91b8bed8de50f33e0f51e</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Inferno/376700</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Inferno 1.0 (376700) properties data file by the EVEMon Development Team
NOT COMPATIBLE with EVEMon prior to version 1.7.0]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-reprocessing-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 June 2012</date>
      <md5>05e4bae06ebacb3ba7acc406c078f065</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Inferno/376700</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Inferno 1.0 (376700) reprocessing data file by the EVEMon Development Team
NOT COMPATIBLE with EVEMon prior to version 1.7.0]]></message>
    </datafile>
    <datafile>
      <name>eve-skills-en-US.xml.gz</name>
      <date>10 June 2012</date>
      <md5>efcdd7e7616983f4fe0363465bca7ca7</md5>
      <url>https://bitbucket.org/BattleClinic/evemon/wiki/updates/datafiles/Inferno/376700</url>
      <message><![CDATA[Inferno 1.0 (376700) skills data file by the EVEMon Development Team
NOT COMPATIBLE with EVEMon prior to version 1.7.0]]></message>
    </datafile>
  </datafiles>
</evemon>